{
    "id": "2ec0ead0058c4370acc5c93e14c12568",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I wouldn’t mind your coming late if you do not wake me ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f5f8108a6b724a979b8784b2846b045d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is independent .............................................. his parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "of",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d08ce8ce4f6c41a28f1bb990c58d5dea"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sonia is the ........................................ of the two girls.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taller",
                "tallest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3f4b27433dd44ebd844ca2430fa83718"
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you please move ..........................................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bit",
                "a bit"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "757bd4dcb47e4c21b9ca9ce14d72f59e"
        },
        {
            "question": "There I saw his Mom ....................................... he said was away.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "83efb32529604bde98521df0c3cc05fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "This chair is quite cheap .......................................... $",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3a5c0ccd276e42489860e4d76bc5ef66"
        },
        {
            "question": "We do not sell things .................................... credit.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "54413b99351e48ecb720cc199fa9dda7"
        },
        {
            "question": "As we labour, so shall we .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reward",
                "be rewarded"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "97819d7a9a3e498294b036b74326d511"
        },
        {
            "question": "I’m ................................................ tired to attend the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5287933784bd476ca42c7f40707aa6f9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been absent ...................................... three days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3fac3893b4494d949ef9709c7ed3d780"
        }
    ]
}